Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Family and Personal Papers, 1841-2000 MS 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Personal (JHJ), 208250 (Box 16-92)
  - Subseries S: Photographs, 210060 (Box 61-78)
    - Individuals, groups, at events, 210338 (Box 67-70)
      - Democratic National Convention, Houston, TX, 1928; 210350 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Eisenhowers, 210351 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - F, 210352 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Fat Stock Show, Houston, TX, 1954; 210353 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Fears family, 210354 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Federal Loan Administration, 210355 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Royal Ferris, 210356 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - G, 210357 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Grant recipients, 210358 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - H, 210359 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Hardin-Simmons University cowboy band, 1941; 210360 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - F.J. Heyne, 210361 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Houston Club groups, 210362 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Houston Endowment, Inc. board and groups, 210363 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Houston Endowment, Inc. staff and past presidents, 210364 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Howard Hughes, 210365 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - I, 210366 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - J, 210367 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Lyndon B. Johnson, 210368 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - K, 210369 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Fiorello LaGuardia, 210370 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - M, 210371 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Gladys Mikell family, 210372 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - W.W. Moore, 210373 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Mc, 210374 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - N, 210375 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - National Bank of Commerce officers, 210378 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - New York Board of Trade banquet, 9/30/1943; 210376 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - E.J. Noble, 210377 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - O, 210379 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - P, 210380 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Edemond Pizzella, JHJ portrait artist, 210381 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - R, 210382 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Franklin D. Roosevelt, 210383 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - S, 210384 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Sam Houston monument dedication, Hermann Park, Houston, TX, 210385 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Eugene Schacher, 210386 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - A.D. Simpson, 210387 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - T, 210388 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Texas A&M University-related, 210389 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Touchdown Club, 210390 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Harry S. Truman, 210391 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - University of Texas-related, 210392 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - unidentified, 210393 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - V, 210394 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - W, 210395 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Edith & Woodrow Wilson, 210397 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - X Y Z, 210398 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - negatives, 210399 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Buildings, 210401 (Box 70-73)
      - 10 East 40th Street, New York City, NY, 210402 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - 40 East 61st Street, New York City, NY, 210403 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - 200 Madison Avenue, New York City, NY, 210405 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - 277 Madison Avenue, New York City, NY, 210406 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - 400 East 57th Street, New York City, NY, 210408 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - 612 Park Avenue, New York City, NY [The Mayfair], 210410 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - 812 Park Avenue, New York City, NY, 210411 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - 950 Fifth Avenue, New York City, NY, 210413 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - 1158 Fifth Avenue, New York City, NY, 210414 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - "Buildings erected by Jesse H. Jones Interests in the city of New York during period 1924 to 1931.", 210415 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - 1114 Texas Avenue, block 70, Houston, TX, 1949; 210416 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - American Laundry, block 82, Houston, TX [718-1/2 Travis], 1929; 210418 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Allen Academy, Jones Memorial Hall, Houston, TX [proposed], 1956; 210421 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - American Red Cedar Chest Manufacturing Co., block 137, Houston, TX [919-921 Main], 210423 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Banker's Mortgage Building, block 81, Houston, TX, 1921-22; 210425 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Banker's Mortgage Building interiors, block 81, Houston, TX, 1921-22; 210426 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Boeing plant, ca. 1940; 210427 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Bond Store, block 93, Houston, TX, 1949; 210428 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Bond Clothes, Fair Building addition, Ft. Worth, TX, 1952; 210429 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Bristol Hotel, block 82, Houston, TX [702 Travis], 1895; 210430 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Bristol Hotel Annex, block 82, Houston, TX [708-712 Travis], 1907; 210431 (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - C&I Building, block 139, Houston, TX [Main @ McKinney], 1947; 210432 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Campbell Hotel, Dallas, TX [New Oxford Hotel], 210433 (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Chevrolet Motor Division,block 467, Houston, TX [Polk @ Dowling], 210434 (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Christie Building, block 44, Houston, TX [proposed], 210435 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Chronicle Building, block 58, Houston, TX, 1908, 1937, 1947; 210436 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Chronicle Building Annex, block 58, Houston, TX, ca. 1916; 210437 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Chronicle Publishing Co. warehouse, Houston, TX, 1953; 210438 (Box 70, Folder 28)
      - Chronicle garage, block 58, Houston, TX, 1976; 210439 (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - City Auditorium, Houston, TX, 1910; 210440 (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Commerce Bank garage, block 82, Houston, TX, 1952; 210441 (Box 70, Folder 31)
      - Commerce Building, block 138, Houston, TX, 1938-39; 210442 (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Commerce Building addition, block 138, Houston, TX, 1947; 210443 (Box 70, Folder 33)
      - Commerce Building garage, block 138, Houston, TX, 210444 (Box 70, Folder 34)
      - Cotton Exchange Building, Houston, TX, 210445 (Box 70, Folder 35)
      - Cozy Theater, block 70, Houston, TX, 210446 (Box 70, Folder 36)
      - Dienstag Building, block 55, Houston, TX, 210447 (Box 70, Folder 37)
      - [Plymouth] Dodge/Jackson Motors, Main Street, Houston, TX, 210448 (Box 70, Folder 38)
      - Dollahite-Levy Building, block 139, Houston, TX [Travis @ McKinney], 1927; 210449 (Box 70, Folder 39)
      - Electric Building, block 137, Houston, TX, 1923, 1926-27; 210451 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Electric Building, Ft. Worth, TX, 210452 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Elm @ St. Paul streets, Dallas, TX, 210454 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Esperson Building, Houston, TX, 210456 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Fair Builidng, Ft. Worth, TX, 1929-30; 210458 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Fair Building addition, Ft. Worth, TX, 1929-30; 210459 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Ft. Worth, TX, 210460 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Foster Building, block 80, Houston, TX, 1913; 210461 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Gas Co. Building, block 80, Houston, TX [Capitol @ Franklin], 1909; 210463 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Gibbs Memorial Library, Mexia, TX, ca. 1955; 210464 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Gibraltar Building, block 71, Houston, TX [1201 Capitol @ San Jacinto], 210466 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Goggan Building, block 81, Houston, TX [originally Texas Co. Bldg.], 1908; 210468 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Gulf Building, Houston, TX [proposals], 210469 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Gulf Building, block 81, Houston, TX [National Bank of Commerce], 1927-28; 210470 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Gulf Building interiors, block 81, Houston, TX, 1927-28; 210481 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Gulf Building addition, block 81, Houston, TX, 1948; 210482 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Gulf Building Annex, block 81, Houston, TX, 1949; 210483 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Haverty Furniture Co., block 79, Houston, TX [Capitol @ Fannin], 1921; 210484 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Hedgecroft Clinic, block 15, Houston, TX, ca. 1959; 210485 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Helberg Building, block 81, Houston, TX, 210486 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Fred J. Heyne Building, University of Houston, Houston, TX, 210487 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Hollywood Theater interiors, Ft. Worth, TX, 210488 (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Hippodrome, Ft. Worth, TX, 210489 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Houston City Hall & Market, 210490 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Houston Club Building, block 82, Houston, TX [Travis @ Rusk], 1954-55; 210491 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Houston Lighting & Power Co., Houston, TX, ca. 1949; 210492 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Houston Terminal Land Co., Houston, TX [Fannin @ Prairie], 210493 (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Houston Terminal Warehouse, block 51, Houston, TX, 1927; 210494 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Hudson Building, block 81, Houston, TX [709 Travis], 210495 (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Jensen Arcade, Pasadena, TX, 210496 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Jesse H. Jones Hall for the Performing Arts, 210498 (Box 72)
        - Construction, 1965-66; 210499 (Box 72, Folder 1)
        - Opening ceremonies, 10/1966; 210500 (Box 72, Folder 2)
        - Opening night concert, 1966; 210501 (Box 72, Folder 3)
        - Sculpture, 1966; 210502 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Jesse H. Jones Hospital, Springfield, TN [became Northcrest Hospital], 210503 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Jesse H. Jones Library, Texas Medical Center, Houston, TX, 1952; 210504 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Jesse H. Jones Lumber Co., Dalhart, TX, ca. 1890; 210505 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Jesse H. Jones Lumber Co., block 139, Houston, TX, 210506 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - John L. Jones Furniture Co., block 82, Houston, TX [716 Travis], 210507 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - K.T.R.H. broadcasting station, Houston, TX, 210508 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Kirby Building, block 137, Houston, TX, 1925-27; 210509 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Kirby Lumber Co., Houston, TX, 210510 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Krupp & Tuffly, block 137, Houston, TX, 1929; 210511 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Kyle Building, block 272, Houston, TX [Main @ Dallas], 1914; 210512 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Lamar Hotel, block 139, Houston, TX, 1927; 210513 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Lamar Hotel Annex, block 139, Houston, TX, 1928; 210514 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Lamar Hotel, block 139, Jones suite, Houston, TX, 210515 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Lerner Shops, New York City, NY, 210516 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Levy property, Ft. Worth, TX, 210517 (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Levy Brothers Building, block 138, Houston, TX, 1928; 210518 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Lowe's Theater, block 139, Houston, TX, 1927; 210519 (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Majestic Theater, block 58, Houston, TX, 210522 (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Mason Building, block 80, Houston, TX, 1915; 210526 (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - McAshan Apartments, block 295, Houston, TX [Main @ Polk], 210520 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - McDade Building, block 60, Houston, TX [Texas @ Louisiana], 1915; 210521 (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Earl McMillian Ford, block 89, Houston, TX, 210523 (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Medical Arts Building, Ft. Worth, TX, 210524 (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Medical Arts garage, block 133, Houston, TX, 1953-54; 210525 (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Metropolitan Theater, block 139, Houston, TX, 1926; 210527 (Box 72, Folder 29)
      - Milam Building, block 58, Houston, TX, 1922; 210528 (Box 72, Folder 30)
      - Morrow's Nut House, Houston, TX, 210529 (Box 72, Folder 31)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, TX, 210530 (Box 72, Folder 32)
      - National Shirt Shop, Houston, TX, 1949; 210531 (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - Oil & Gas Building, Ft. Worth, TX, 210532 (Box 72, Folder 34)
      - Pearce's Theater, block 81, Houston, TX [700 Main], ca. 1916; 210533 (Box 72, Folder 35)
      - Proposed apartment building, Ft. Worth, TX, 1927; 210534 (Box 72, Folder 36)
      - Randolph Building, block 67, Houston, TX, 1911; 210535 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Reagan State Bank, 210536 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Reynolds Building, Ft. Worth, TX, 210537 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Rice Building, block 57, Houston,TX [Main @ Texas], 1894; 210538 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Rice Hotel, block 57, Houston, TX, 1912, 1923; 210539 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Rice Hotel drive-in entrance building, block 57, Houston, TX, 1958-59; 210540 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Rice Hotel garage, block 59, Houston, TX, 1948; 210541 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Rice Hotel laundry, block 89, Houston, TX, 210542 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Roxford Apartments, block 81, Houston, TX, ca. 1918; 210543 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Rusk Building, block 80, Houston, TX, 1915-16; 210544 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Rusk Hotel, block 81, Houston, TX, 1915; 210545 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - San Jacinto Monument, Deer Park, TX, 210546 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Sayers Motors, block 89, Houston, TX, 210547 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Simms property, Cleveland oak tree, block 94, Houston, TX [Rusk @ San Jacinto], 1959; 210548 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Smith-Waltrip-Hudson-Essex Building, Ft. Worth, TX, 210549 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Statler Hotel, Chicago, IL, 210550 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Sterne Building, block 33, Houston, TX, 210551 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Sterrick Building, Memphis, TN, 1929; 210552 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - St. Paul's Methodist Church, Houston, TX, 210553 (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - H.D. Taylor Lumber Co., 210554 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Texas A&M University, College Station, TX, 210555 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Texas Co. Building, Houston, TX, 210556 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Texas Medical Center, Houston, TX, 210557 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Texas National Bank concept, Houston, TX [1300 Main], 1953; 210558 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Texas State Hotel, block 80, Houston, TX, 1926; 210559 (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - Union National Bank, block 20, Houston, TX [Main @ Congress], 210560 (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - United Gas Co., block 138, Houston, TX, 1930; 210561 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Walker Furniture/Bus station, block 82, Houston, TX, 1923; 210562 (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - Washington, DC, 210564 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - Wells Fargo Building, block 67, Houston, TX, 1913-14; 210565 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Worth Hotel and Publix Theater, Ft. Worth, TX, 1926; 210566 (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - Yellow Cab Co., block 60, Houston, TX, 210563 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified, 210569 (Box 73)
      - Car elevator, 210570 (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Dallas-Ft. Worth, 210571 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - Lumber yard, 210572 (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Proposals, 210573 (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - Skyscrapers, 210574 (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Downtown Houston, 210575 (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Houston various locations, 210576 (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Proofs and negatives, 210577 (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - Oversize, 210578 (Box 74)
      - Royal Ferris, 210579 (Box 74)
      - Mr. & Mrs. Gibbs [Mary Gibbs Jones' parents], 210580 (Box 74)
      - Mary Gibbs [Jones] as young girl (2 copies), 210581 (Box 74)
      - Franklin D. Roosevelt, 210582 (Box 74)
      - Jesse H. Jones (younger), 210583 (Box 74)
      - Jesse H. Jones (to Gladys Mikell), 1944; 210584 (Box 74)
      - Jesse H. Jones (eating at desk), 210585 (Box 74)
      - John Beck (in Army uniform), 210586 (Box 74)
      - Tilford Jones (oval), 210587 (Box 74)
      - Unidentified skyscraper rendering, 210588 (Box 74)
      - Lamar Hotel, 210589 (Box 74)
      - Medical Arts parking garage, 210590 (Box 74)
      - National Bank of Commerce (interiors & exteriors), 210591 (Box 75)
      - Gulf Building, 210592 (Box 75)
      - San Jacinto Monument, 210593 (Box 75)
      - 1114 Texas Ave., 210594 (Box 75)
      - South Texas National Bank, 210595 (Box 75)
      - Rice Hotel, 210596 (Box 75)
      - Jones Hall, 210597 (Box 75)
      - Market Square, 210598 (Box 75)
      - Downtown Houston, 210599 (Box 75)
      - Sam Houston monument and surrounds, 1926; 210600 (Box 75)
      - Deepwater Ranch on Ship Channel (aerial), 210601 (Box 75)
      - Deepwater Ranch photo album, 210602 (Box 76)
      - Will Rogers photo album, 12/25/1957; 210603 (Box 77)
    - Texas-related, 210604 (Box 78)
      - Houston aerials, 210605 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Houston Ship Channel, 210606 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Houston Shipbuilding Corp., 210607 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Ranching and farming, 210609 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Early oil fields, 210610 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Texas Centennial, 210612 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - S.N. Johnson tract, Webb County, 210614 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - William Vince survey, 210615 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Harris & Wilson grant, 210617 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - World War I: Military hospitals in France, 210618 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Album: The Colonel Goes Fishing, Cape Vincent, NY, Labor Day 1953, 210748 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Subseries T: Realia/memorabilia (oversize), 210620 (Box 79-94)
    - Scrapbook pages/newsclippings, 210621 (Box 79)
    - Framed Chase/Gulf Building newstory & souvenir booklet, 2003; 210622 (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Site surveys for buildings and properties, 210623 (Box 80)
      - Deepwater, TX/Deepwater Ranch, 210624 (Box 80)
      - City of Houston buildings plot map (2), 1929, n.d.; 210625 (Box 80)
      - Hotel building, Main St. @ Lamar Ave, 16th floor plan, 1927; 210626 (Box 80)
      - Hotel building, Main St. @ Lamar Ave. 16th floor mechanical plan, 1927; 210641 (Box 80)
      - Levy Brothers Co. 5th floor plan, 210627 (Box 80)
      - Unidentifed office building 9th-11th floor plans, 1935; 210628 (Box 80)
      - Ft. Worth theater and hotel study plans, 1925; 210629 (Box 80)
      - Worth Hotel & theater plot plan, Ft. Worth, TX, 210633 (Box 80)
      - Plot plan of block no. 139, Houston, TX, 1960; 210630 (Box 80)
      - Humble Oil Field property ownership map, 1915; 210631 (Box 80)
      - Banker's Mortgage Co. survey of block 59, Houston, TX, 1946; 210634 (Box 80)
      - Plot plan of block 137, Houston, TX, 210635 (Box 80)
      - Plan of block 93, Houston, TX, 1943; 210636 (Box 80)
      - Houston Terminal Warehouse & Cold Storage Co. fee property plan, Houston, TX, 1958; 210637 (Box 80)
      - Section of business district of the City of Houston properties plan and listings, 1929; 210638 (Box 80)
      - Street plan showing properties, downtown district, Houston, TX, 210639 (Box 80)
      - Sterrick Building, Inc., Memphis, TN bond issue advertisement, 1929; 210640 (Box 80)
      - Survey of block 70, Houston, TX, 1948; 210632 (Box 80)
      - 200 Madison Avenue, New York building description flyer, 1925-26; 210646 (Box 80)
      - Mayfair House, 65th @ Park Avenue, New York, floor plans and description, 210647 (Box 80)
      - Portion of Houston, TX business district (along Main St.), 210648 (Box 80)
      - Store building, Main St. @ Capitol Avenue store first floor plan, 210649 (Box 80)
      - Main St. elevation of building, 1922; 210650 (Box 80)
    - Political cartoons, 210651 (Box 81)
    - Texas flag 19" x 12", 210652 (Box 81)
    - Graphic for "Brother, Can You Spare a Million?", 210654 (Box 81)
    - Certificates, 210655 (Box 81)
      - Reconstruction Finance Corporation resolutions (copies), 1930s; 210656 (Box 81)
      - Honorary degrees, 210657
        - Southwestern University, Georgetown, TX: Doctor of Laws, 1925, 210658 (Box 81)
        - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas, College Station, TX: Doctor of Laws, 1936, 210659 (Box 81)
        - Northwestern University, Evanston-Chicago, IL: Doctor of Laws, 1942, 210660 (Box 81)
      - Philosophical Society of Texas membership, 1939, 210661 (Box 81)
      - High Hat Award, 1938, 210662 (Box 81)
      - Book of Golden Deed of the Exchange Club of Fort Worth, Texas enrollment, 1928; 210663 (Box 81)
    - White House day book entry for Nov. 12, 1917 'dinner, Mr. Jesse Jones..." (copy), 210664 (Box 81)
    - Bibles, 210684 (Box 82)
    - Man of the Hour and Year 1928, 210685 (Box 83)
    - California Commission Golden Gate International Exposition appreciation plaque, 210686 (Box 83)
    - Lamar Hotel plate, 210689 (Box 84)
    - European trip itinerary and maps, 7/23-8/19/1952; 210691 (Box 85)
    - Jesse H. Jones Hall for the Performing Arts, October 1966, Houston commemorative coins (ca. 100), 210692 (Box 85)
    - "A Shootin' Po' Soul" by Nash Buckingham for Mr. Jesse Jones, 210693 (Box 85)
    - "In Remembrance" - Mrs. Mary Gibbs Jones memorial book (funeral), 1962; 210694 (Box 85)
    - Mary Gibbs Jones bookplate (attached to book cover board), 210695 (Box 85)
    - Keys to lockers in vault, Bankers Mortgage Co., 210696 (Box 85)
    - Framed invitation: The Citizens of Austin invite Mr. E. Pizzella and Lady to Reception and Dance in honor of Honorable Jesse Holman Jones at Gregory Gymnasium, Monday evening, Oct. 7, 1935, at eight o'clock following the dedication of his painting by the State Senate, afternoon of October seventh Verso: red pencil sketch of Mary Gibbs Jones by Pizzella, 210697 (Box 85)
    - Date books/year books: 1933-38, 40, 43, 44, 48, 210698 (Box 86)
    - Ledgers, 210699 (Box 87-90)
      - Trust estate, 1933-47; 210700 (Box 87)
      - Cash journals (4), 1933-48; 210701 (Box 88)
      - Balance sheets for Houston Endowment, Inc., 1973; 210703 (Box 88)
      - Cash, 1913-1922; 210704 (Box 89)
      - Plot book-Southern Loan & Investment Co., 210705 (Box 90)
      - Cash received & cash disbursements, 1949-1953; 210706 (Box 90)
      - Accounts (2), 1923-1930; 210707 (Box 90)
    - Audio/Visual, 210708 (Box 91-92)
      - VHS, 210721 (Box 91)
        - Jesse Holman Jones original house, cemetery, vhs_09; 210722 (Box 91)
          Scope and Contents
          This digitized video file consists of one master copy mp4, one access copy mp4, and jpegs of the VHS as well as transfer metadata.
        - "My baby movies", vhs_07; 210723 (Box 91)
        - "A Cavalcade of Texas", 1939-40; vhs_06; 210724 (Box 91)
        - John T. Jones retrospective on Jesse H. Jones (2 copies), 2/4/1992; vhs_08; 210725 (Box 91)
        - Jesse H. Jones centennial celebration, 11/10/1998; vhs_10; 210726 (Box 91)
      - DVD, 210727 (Box 91)
        - Jesse H. Jones original house, cemetery, 210728 (Box 91)
        - "A Cavalcade of Texas", 1939-40; 210729 (Box 91)
        - Obituaries on death of JHJ (2 copies), 6/1956; 210730 (Box 91)
        - John T. Jones retrospective on Jesse H. Jones, 1992; 210731 (Box 91)
        - Jesse H. Jones centennial celebration, 11/10/1998; 210732 (Box 91)
        - Audrey Jones Beck galleries (2 copies), 210733 (Box 91)
      - Aluminum and acetate records, 210734 (Box 92)
        - "Pre-flight training in American schools" (sides 1,2,3,4), 9/10/1942; lp_02; 210735 (Box 92)
          This digitized audio file consists of one master copy wav, one access copy mp3, and jpegs of the record as well as transfer metadata. lp_01 which comprosed part 1 and 2 of the speech was damaged and could not be digitized.
        - "Orville Wright testimonial dinner" (sides 3,4,5,6,9,10,11), 12/17/1943; lp_03, lp_04, lp_05, lp_06; 210736 (Box 92)
          These digitized audio files consist of one master copy wav, one access copy mp3, and jpegs of the record as well as transfer metadata.
        - "25 anniversary of air mail service" (sides 3,4,5,6,7,8), 5/15/1943; lp_07, lp_08, lp_09; 210737 (Box 92)
        - "What the War Will Bring" (sides 1,2,3,4,5,6,9,10) 2 broken, 4/3/1944; lp_10, lp_11; 210738 (Box 92)
          These digitized audio files consist of one master copy wav, one access copy mp3, and jpegs of the record as well as transfer metadata. Digitized discs include parts 5, 6, 9, 10. All others were broken.
        - "National Press Club luncheon" (sides 1,2,3), 7/21/1938; lp_12, lp_13; 210739 (Box 92)
        - "Work of the RFC in ending the Depression" (sides 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8), 11/23/1936; lp_14, lp_15, lp_16, lp_17; 210740 (Box 92)
        - "Reception to Howard Hughes", 7/15/1938; lp_18; 210741 (Box 92)